opinions and not get interrupted. So for
me personally I tend to
kind of call out let's say the other
person. Um because I think in my home or
relationship dynamic it's just a lot of
just self-awareness because a lot of
people don't know they're interrupting
others, right? So sometimes it's like,
"Okay, yeah, hold your thought. Just
like hold on for like 30 more seconds or
however long. Just like let this person
finish their spiel." And it's funny,
people don't tend to have a good um
signal because I've had multiple
conversations with my partner too where
he's like, "Oh, I thought you were
done." I'm like, "No, that pause was not
long enough in my point, but they
interpreted as a different
These these are exactly the types of
things that like I've run into in my
life." And I said, I wish there was a
way for us to have a common language
about those pains or at least some way
to remind us and not be punitive, but
just have some way to be like,
this is how I talk and these are sort of
my break points or these are where I
would like to jump in or something like
that.
Right. Right.